[
  {
    "question": "What school does Harry Potter attend?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Durmstrang", "Beauxbatons", "Castelobruxo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the headmaster of the school Harry attends?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Minerva McGonagall", "Cornelius Fudge", "Madame Maxime"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Harry Potters greatest enemy?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Dolores Umbridge", "Severus Snape", "Nagini"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Harry Potters closest friend (male)?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Neville Longbottom", "Charlie Weasley", "Cedric Diggory"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Harry Potters closest friend (female)?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Luna Lovegood", "Cho Chang", "Parvati Patil"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What game, using flying broomsticks, is played by wizards?",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Headless Hunt",
      "Winged Horse Races",
      "Wizarding Skittles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What teacher, despised by many, teaches potions?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Horace Slughorn", "Gilderoy Lockhart", "Dolores Umbridge"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of animal is Harry's pet?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Frog", "Rat", "Cat"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who tells Harry that he is, in fact, a wizard?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Albus Dumbledore", "Petunia Dursley", "Cornelius Fudge"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who wrote the Harry Potter series?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["N K Jemisin", "Roald Dahl", "Terry Pratchet"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what country are the books set?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["France", "New Zealand", "Italy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What platform does the train to the school depart from?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["9 & 4/5", "10", "8 & 3/4"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of creature is Dobby?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Goblin", "Giamt", "Thestral"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What house is Draco Malfoy a part of?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Hufflepuff", "Gryffindor", "Ravenclaw"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What prison does Sirius Black escape from?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Alcatraz", "St Brutus", "Erkstag"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In this game, what is Harry Potter's position?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Beater", "Keeper", "Chaser"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Harry's mothers name?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Jasmine", "Lilac", "Rose"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What house has the house colour of blue?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Sytherin", "Hufflepuff", "Gryffindor"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is George Weasley's twin?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Charlie Weasley", "Bill Weaasley", "Percy Weasley"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Harry's pet?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Crookshanks", "Scabbers", "Trevor"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are Tom Riddle's diary and Rowena Ravenclaw's diadem?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Deathly Hallows", "Curses", "Emblems"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature, from the Chamber of Secrets, paralyzes and kills students in Harry's second year?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Spider", "Flobber Worms", "Hippogriff"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who dies during the Triwizard Tornament?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Victor Krum", "Dobby", "Mad Eye Moody"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What will \"suck all the happiness from you\"?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Death Eater", "Thestral", "Boggart"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who haunts the girls bathroom?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["The Grey Lady", "Bloody Baron", "Peeves"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has radish earrings?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Tonks Nymphadora", "Hermione Granger", "Hannah Abbott"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the spell \"Alohomora\" do",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Cast light", "Summon objects", "Levitate things"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Voldemorts snake?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Hedwig", "Buckbeak", "Marvolo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the mischievous poltergeist that wreaks havoc throughout the school?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Moaning Myrtle", "Nearly Headless Nick", "Kreacher"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What ball does the school hold?",
    "wrongAnswers": ["Christmas Ball", "Triwizard Ball", "Summer Ball"]
  }
]
